{"questions":[
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950730",
  "correct_answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Ralph Fiennes",
    "Brian Cox",
    "Kiefer Sutherland"
  ],
  "question": "Which actor has starred in films including Titanic and The Revenant?",
  "tags": [
    "acting",
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "625698719da29df7b05f7287",
  "correct_answer": "Loki",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Iron Man",
    "Black Panther",
    "Spiderman"
  ],
  "question": "In the Marvel Cinematic Unvierse, which character is played by Tom Hiddleston?",
  "tags": [
    "mcu",
    "film",
    "acting",
    "marvel",
    "comics",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbde",
  "correct_answer": "\"Very nice!\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"I'm walking here! I'm walking here!\"",
    "\"The stuff that dreams are made of.\"",
    "\"A martini. Shaken, not stirred.\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Borat'?",
  "tags": [
    "quotes",
    "film",
    "general_knowledge",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa61",
  "correct_answer": "Heath Ledger",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Josh Brolin",
    "Robert Downey Jr.",
    "Philip Seymour Hoffman"
  ],
  "question": "Who won the 2008 Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for playing the role of Joker in The Dark Knight?",
  "tags": [
    "academy_awards",
    "film",
    "batman",
    "dc",
    "comics",
    "acting",
    "general_knowledge",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950713",
  "correct_answer": "Will Smith",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Brian Cox",
    "Ralph Fiennes",
    "Ryan Reynolds"
  ],
  "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Suicide Squad and Men in Black?",
  "tags": [
    "acting",
    "film",
    "general_knowledge",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "62573f009da29df7b05f7381",
  "correct_answer": "The Matrix",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Pulp Fiction",
    "Forrest Gump",
    "Joker"
  ],
  "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A hacker discovers the life he knows is the elaborate deception of an evil cyber-intelligence.'",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9506fb",
  "correct_answer": "Matthew McConaughey",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Ryan Reynolds",
    "Jim Carrey",
    "Hugh Jackman"
  ],
  "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Interstellar and The Wolf of Wall Street?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "acting",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "625741379da29df7b05f740e",
  "correct_answer": "Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Die Hard",
    "The Departed",
    "The Truman Show"
  ],
  "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A blacksmith teams up with an eccentric pirate to save his love.'",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbeb",
  "correct_answer": "\"I have had it with these mother—— snakes on this mother—— plane!\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"Not my tempo.\"",
    "\"Oh, Jerry, don't let's ask for the moon. We have the stars.\"",
    "\"Tell 'em to go out there with all they got and win just one for the Gipper.\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Snakes on a Plane'?",
  "tags": [
    "quotes",
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc28",
  "correct_answer": "\"My mama always said life was like a box of chocolates. You never know what you're gonna get.\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"Very nice!\"",
    "\"Say hello to my little friend!\"",
    "\"Nobody makes me bleed my own blood. Nobody!\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Forrest Gump'?",
  "tags": [
    "quotes",
    "film",
    "general_knowledge",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "625740ec9da29df7b05f7402",
  "correct_answer": "Jaws",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "The Silence of the Lambs",
    "The Good, the Bad and the Ugly",
    "Platoon"
  ],
  "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A killer shark unleashes chaos on a beach community.'",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f914",
  "correct_answer": "The Silence of the Lambs",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Casablanca",
    "A Nightmare on Elm Street",
    "Taxi Driver"
  ],
  "question": "Which film contains the character 'Hannibal Lecter'?",
  "tags": [
    "acting",
    "film",
    "horror",
    "general_knowledge",
    "fictitious_characters",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9507aa",
  "correct_answer": "Tom Hanks",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Leonardo DiCaprio",
    "Tom Cruise",
    "Sean Connery"
  ],
  "question": "Which actor has featured in films including Forrest Gump and Saving Private Ryan?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "acting",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc53",
  "correct_answer": "\"May the Force be with you.\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"You’re going to go through life thinking that girls don’t like you because you’re a nerd. And I want you to know, from the bottom of my heart, that won’t be true. It’ll be because you’re an a**hole.\"",
    "\"Shane. Shane. Come back!\"",
    "\"Elementary, my dear Watson.\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Star Wars'?",
  "tags": [
    "quotes",
    "film",
    "general_knowledge",
    "star_wars",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8d9",
  "correct_answer": "Bruce Willis",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "John Travolta",
    "Sean Penn",
    "Al Pacino"
  ],
  "question": "Which actor played the role of John McClane in Die Hard?",
  "tags": [
    "acting",
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fadd",
  "correct_answer": "Tom Hanks",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Morgan Freeman",
    "Nigel Hawthorne",
    "Paul Newman"
  ],
  "question": "Who won the 1994 Academy Award for Best Leading Actor for playing the role of Forrest Gump in Forrest Gump?",
  "tags": [
    "academy_awards",
    "acting",
    "film",
    "general_knowledge",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "62573f569da29df7b05f7396",
  "correct_answer": "Back to the Future",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "The Truman Show",
    "Raiders of the Lost Ark",
    "Forrest Gump"
  ],
  "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A high school student is sent thirty years into the past in a time-traveling car.'",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fadc",
  "correct_answer": "Anthony Hopkins",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Warren Beatty",
    "Robert De Niro",
    "Nick Nolte"
  ],
  "question": "Who won the 1991 Academy Award for Best Leading Actor for playing the role of Dr. Hannibal Lecter in The Silence of the Lambs?",
  "tags": [
    "academy_awards",
    "acting",
    "film",
    "general_knowledge",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc37",
  "correct_answer": "\"There's no place like home.\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"Oh, Jerry, don't let's ask for the moon. We have the stars.\"",
    "\"I’m already pregnant. So, what other shenanigans could I get myself into?\"",
    "\"This is the day you will always remember as the day you almost caught Captain Jack Sparrow!\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'The Wizard of Oz'?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "quotes",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f907",
  "correct_answer": "Raiders of the Lost Ark",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "The Graduate",
    "Alien",
    "The Usual Suspects"
  ],
  "question": "Which film contains the character 'Indiana Jones'?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "fictitious_characters",
    "general_knowledge",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "6257413a9da29df7b05f740f",
  "correct_answer": "A kindhearted street urchin and a power-hungry Grand Vizier vie for a magic lamp.",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Simba and his father are targeted by his uncle, who wants to ascend the throne himself.",
    "Two soldiers race to deliver a message that will stop 1,600 men from walking into a deadly trap.",
    "Two grifters team up to pull off the ultimate con."
  ],
  "question": "What is the plot of the movie Aladdin?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbdb",
  "correct_answer": "\"This is the day you will always remember as the day you almost caught Captain Jack Sparrow!\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"My precious.\"",
    "\"I'll get you, my pretty, and your little dog, too!\"",
    "\"Keep your friends close, but your enemies closer.\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl'?",
  "tags": [
    "quotes",
    "film",
    "general_knowledge",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "62573fa49da29df7b05f73a8",
  "correct_answer": "An archaeologist is hired by the government to find the Ark of the Covenant.",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "On a journey to find the cure for a curse, a boy finds himself in the middle of a war.",
    "A Tramp struggles to live in modern industrial society with the help of a young homeless woman.",
    "A 12-year-old is taken in by a professional assassin after her family is murdered."
  ],
  "question": "What is the plot of the movie Raiders of the Lost Ark?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f90c",
  "correct_answer": "The Lord of the Rings",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "The Searchers",
    "Ghost",
    "My Favorite Year"
  ],
  "question": "Which film contains the character 'Gollum'?",
  "tags": [
    "fictitious_characters",
    "film",
    "general_knowledge",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "62573efd9da29df7b05f7380",
  "correct_answer": "A man becomes concerned for his Jewish workforce after witnessing their persecution by the Nazis.",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "In order to power the city, beasts have to scare children so that they scream.",
    "A girl wanders into a world ruled by gods, witches, and spirits, where humans are changed into beasts.",
    "King Arthur and his Knights embark on a search for a religious relic."
  ],
  "question": "What is the plot of the movie Schindler's List?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "62573f8c3d2f5c16bfb88334",
  "correct_answer": "The crew of a spacecraft encounter a deadly lifeform after investigating a transmission.",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "The life of the lawyer who became the famed leader of the Indian revolts against the British rule.",
    "An insurance representative lets a housewife seduce him into a scheme of insurance fraud and murder.",
    "After the death of a tycoon, reporters scramble to uncover the meaning of his final utterance."
  ],
  "question": "What is the plot of the movie Alien?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc4b",
  "correct_answer": "\"I'm gonna make him an offer he can't refuse.\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"I love the smell of napalm in the morning.\"",
    "\"I have nipples Greg. Could you milk me?\"",
    "\"Elementary, my dear Watson.\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'The Godfather'?",
  "tags": [
    "quotes",
    "film",
    "general_knowledge",
    "cult_films",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9507b4",
  "correct_answer": "Arnold Schwarzenegger",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Sylvester Stallone",
    "Jason Statham",
    "Chuck Norris"
  ],
  "question": "Which action star has featured in both Terminator and Predator?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "acting",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950797",
  "correct_answer": "Robert Downey Jr.",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Chris Evans",
    "Chris Hemsworth",
    "Tom Holland"
  ],
  "question": "Which actor played the role of Iron Man in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
  "tags": [
    "acting",
    "film",
    "marvel",
    "comics",
    "mcu",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc03",
  "correct_answer": "\"Forget it, Jake, it's Chinatown.\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"I could do this all day\"",
    "\"You shall not pass!\"",
    "\"Mother of mercy, is this the end of Rico?\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Chinatown'?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "quotes",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "62573f079da29df7b05f7383",
  "correct_answer": "A chaotic clown causes a masked vigilante one of his greatest tests.",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "A stranger joins forces with a desperado to protect a widow from an assassin.",
    "A woman works with a hardened boxing trainer to become a professional.",
    "A suburban father has a mid-life crisis after becoming infatuated with his daughter's friend."
  ],
  "question": "What is the plot of the movie The Dark Knight?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501fe",
  "correct_answer": "Quentin Tarantino",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Steven Spielberg",
    "Woody Allen",
    "Martin Scorsese"
  ],
  "question": "Which director directed Pulp Fiction?",
  "tags": [
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9507bb",
  "correct_answer": "Clint Eastwood",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Matt Damon",
    "Robert De Niro",
    "Sean Connery"
  ],
  "question": "Which actor has featured in films including The Good, the Bad and the Ugly and Million Dollar Baby?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "acting",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "62573f899da29df7b05f73a1",
  "correct_answer": "A young man joins forces with an old man, a cocky pilot, a beast and two robots to save the galaxy.",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "The son of a city's mastermind falls in love with a working-class prophet.",
    "After two male musicians witness a murder, they flee in an all-female band disguised as women.",
    "Violence and mayhem ensue after a man stumbles upon more than two million dollars."
  ],
  "question": "What is the plot of the movie Star Wars?",
  "tags": [
    "film"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f922",
  "correct_answer": "Austin Powers: International Man of Mystery",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Die Hard",
    "The Adventures of Robin Hood",
    "Pulp Fiction"
  ],
  "question": "Which film contains the character 'Dr. Evil'?",
  "tags": [
    "acting",
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9507ad",
  "correct_answer": "Tom Hanks",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Ewan McGregor",
    "Will Smith",
    "Tom Cruise"
  ],
  "question": "Which actor has featured in films including Forrest Gump and Apollo 13?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "acting",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc0f",
  "correct_answer": "\"Take your stinking paws off me, you damned dirty ape.\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"Mrs. Robinson, you're trying to seduce me. Aren't you?\"",
    "\"Toga! Toga!\"",
    "\"Attica! Attica!\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Planet of the Apes'?",
  "tags": [
    "quotes",
    "film",
    "general_knowledge",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "62573fee9da29df7b05f73b7",
  "correct_answer": "Toy Story",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Pan's Labyrinth",
    "The Exorcist",
    "Gandhi"
  ],
  "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A cowboy doll is threatened when a new spaceman figure supplants him as top toy.'",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc11",
  "correct_answer": "\"Mrs. Robinson, you're trying to seduce me. Aren't you?\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"Soylent Green is people!\"",
    "\"Round up the usual suspects.\"",
    "\"Just keep swimming.\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'The Graduate'?",
  "tags": [
    "quotes",
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "624dba55cd90beeca353156c",
  "correct_answer": "Daniel Craig",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Sean Connery",
    "Roger Moore",
    "Timothy Dalton"
  ],
  "question": "Who played the role of James Bond in Skyfall?",
  "tags": [
    "james_bond",
    "film",
    "acting",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "625698689da29df7b05f7285",
  "correct_answer": "Captain America",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Thor",
    "The Collector",
    "Spiderman"
  ],
  "question": "Chris Evans plays the role of which character in the Marvel Cinematic Unvierse?",
  "tags": [
    "mcu",
    "film",
    "acting",
    "marvel",
    "comics",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc0d",
  "correct_answer": "\"Here's Johnny!\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"Nobody puts Baby in a corner.\"",
    "\"You’re going to go through life thinking that girls don’t like you because you’re a nerd. And I want you to know, from the bottom of my heart, that won’t be true. It’ll be because you’re an a**hole.\"",
    "\"Yo, Adrian!\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'The Shining'?",
  "tags": [
    "quotes",
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbc9",
  "correct_answer": "\"This is Sparta!\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"Elementary, my dear Watson.\"",
    "\"I have always depended on the kindness of strangers.\"",
    "\"I love the smell of napalm in the morning.\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film '300'?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "quotes",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "625698549da29df7b05f7280",
  "correct_answer": "Tony Stark",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "The Grandmaster",
    "Alexander Pierce",
    "Vision"
  ],
  "question": "In the Marvel Cinematic Unvierse, which character is played by Robert Downey Jr.?",
  "tags": [
    "mcu",
    "film",
    "acting",
    "marvel",
    "comics",
    "general_knowledge",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9507c5",
  "correct_answer": "Harrison Ford",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Brad Pitt",
    "Michael Fassbender",
    "John Cusack"
  ],
  "question": "Which actor has starred in films including Star Wars and Blade Runner?",
  "tags": [
    "acting",
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbe0",
  "correct_answer": "\"Nobody makes me bleed my own blood. Nobody!\"",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "\"Are you not entertained?\"",
    "\"I have had it with these mother—— snakes on this mother—— plane!\"",
    "\"What is this? A center for ants? How can we be expected to teach children to learn how to read…if they can’t even fit inside the building?\""
  ],
  "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Dodgeball: A True Underdog Story'?",
  "tags": [
    "quotes",
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "625740f39da29df7b05f7404",
  "correct_answer": "A young girl and her dog are swept away by a tornado from their Kansas farm to a magical land.",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "A man with short-term memory loss attempts to track down his wife's murderer.",
    "The jury in a murder trial is frustrated by a member whose caution forces them to consider the evidence.",
    "A former neo-nazi tries to prevent his brother from going down the same path that he did."
  ],
  "question": "What is the plot of the movie The Wizard of Oz?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501f0",
  "correct_answer": "Christopher Nolan",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Steven Spielberg",
    "Woody Allen",
    "Martin Scorsese"
  ],
  "question": "Which director directed Interstellar?",
  "tags": [
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "6256986c9da29df7b05f7286",
  "correct_answer": "Chris Hemsworth",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "Jon Favreau",
    "John Slattery",
    "Tom Holland"
  ],
  "question": "The role of Thor in the Marvel Cinematic Universe is played by which actor?",
  "tags": [
    "mcu",
    "film",
    "acting",
    "marvel",
    "comics",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
  "category": "Film & TV",
  "id": "625740839da29df7b05f73e3",
  "correct_answer": "After his son is captured and taken to Sydney, a clownfish sets out on a journey to bring him home.",
  "incorrect_answers": [
    "A prince cursed to spend his days as a monster sets out to regain his humanity.",
    "After he becomes a quadriplegic, an aristocrat hires a young man to be his caregiver.",
    "A high school student is sent thirty years into the past in a time-traveling car."
  ],
  "question": "What is the plot of the movie Finding Nemo?",
  "tags": [
    "film",
    "film_and_tv"
  ],
  "type": "Multiple Choice",
  "difficulty": "easy"
  },{
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60ad50d1a5e051325a6c",
    "correct_answer": "Italy",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Equatorial Guinea",
      "Spain",
      "Austria"
    ],
    "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Lasagna?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502e3",
    "correct_answer": "Greece ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Italy",
      "Russia",
      "Pakistan"
    ],
    "question": "In which country would you expect to be served a yoghurt-based starter called 'tzatziki'?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950224",
    "correct_answer": "Mushrooms ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Garlic",
      "Onion",
      "Cabbage"
    ],
    "question": "Which Vegetable Can Be Oyster, Chestnut, or Shitaki?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951635",
    "correct_answer": "Bread",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Cheese",
      "Fruit",
      "Nut"
    ],
    "question": " What type of food is pitta?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f95163b",
    "correct_answer": "Green",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Blue",
      "Yellow",
      "Red"
    ],
    "question": " What colour is the flesh of an avocado?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950285",
    "correct_answer": "Grog ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Guppy",
      "Roller",
      "Meal"
    ],
    "question": "What was the name of the highly diluted rum that was once given to British sailors?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f95164a",
    "correct_answer": "Lettuce",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Egg",
      "Tomato",
      "Bread"
    ],
    "question": " Iceberg, Boston, and Bibb are types of what?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502f6",
    "correct_answer": "Bread ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Cheese",
      "Cake",
      "Wine"
    ],
    "question": "Bruschetta is what?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950298",
    "correct_answer": "Michelin Star",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "North Star",
      "Flavour Star",
      "Prestige Star"
    ],
    "question": "What Type Of Star Is Awarded To Restaurants Where The food Is Of Exceptional Quality?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951555",
    "correct_answer": "Samosa",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Pakora",
      "Curry",
      "Bhaji"
    ],
    "question": "What name is given to an Indian deep fried triangular pastry?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "india",
      "pastry",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951627",
    "correct_answer": "Morocco ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Italy",
      "France",
      "Brazil"
    ],
    "question": "A Tagine Is A Dish That Originated In Which Country?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951617",
    "correct_answer": "100",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "0",
      "273",
      "71"
    ],
    "question": "At What Temperature Centigrade Does Water Boil At?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951954",
    "correct_answer": "Pigs in blankets",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Little weiners",
      "Swine rolls",
      "Porkos"
    ],
    "question": "What is the popular name for little baked sausages wrapped in rashers of streaky bacon?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "names",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95029f",
    "correct_answer": "Parmesan ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Wensleydale",
      "Stilton",
      "Gorgonzola"
    ],
    "question": "What sort of cheese would you sprinkle on spaghetti?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "italy",
      "general_knowledge",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95022f",
    "correct_answer": "Guinness ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Porters",
      "Doogals",
      "Old Black"
    ],
    "question": "Which stout is Dublin world-famous for?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950214",
    "correct_answer": "Roald Dahl ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Charles Dickens",
      "Jacqueline Wilson",
      "Morgan Scott"
    ],
    "question": "Who wrote the book Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95023e",
    "correct_answer": "Haggis ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Neeps and Tatties",
      "Pizza Crunch",
      "Cullen Skink"
    ],
    "question": "Which Scottish Dish Is Boiled In The Stomach Lining Of A Sheep?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9515e9",
    "correct_answer": "Kosher ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Deli",
      "Vegan",
      "Halal"
    ],
    "question": "Food that is permitted to be eaten under Jewish dietary laws is known as what?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "judaism",
      "religion",
      "words",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c607b50d1a5e051325a5e",
    "correct_answer": "England",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Mexico",
      "Philippines",
      "Spain"
    ],
    "question": "Fish & Chips is a dish that is most associated with which part of the world?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60b150d1a5e051325a6d",
    "correct_answer": "Pizza",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Dim Sum",
      "Cou Cou and Flying Fish",
      "Kabuli Pulao"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these dishes would you most expect to find in Italy?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "italy",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60fc50d1a5e051325a81",
    "correct_answer": "Spain",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Denmark",
      "Cambodia",
      "Costa Rica"
    ],
    "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Paella?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60f550d1a5e051325a7f",
    "correct_answer": "Scotland",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Estonia",
      "Hungary",
      "Thailand"
    ],
    "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Haggis?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9515cc",
    "correct_answer": "Spain ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Italy",
      "France",
      "Russia"
    ],
    "question": "From which country does the dish paella originate?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60c095b12387e142c79b",
    "correct_answer": "Ramen",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Ceviche",
      "Plov",
      "Chilli Crab"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these dishes would you most expect to find in Japan?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c608650d1a5e051325a61",
    "correct_answer": "France",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Austria",
      "Benin",
      "North Africa"
    ],
    "question": "Crêpes are most associated with which part of the world?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950246",
    "correct_answer": "Avocado ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Cucumber",
      "Tomato",
      "Mango"
    ],
    "question": "Which Is The Main Ingredient Of Guacamole?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60d150d1a5e051325a75",
    "correct_answer": "Mexico",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Bhutan",
      "Japan",
      "Brazil"
    ],
    "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served a taco?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502e6",
    "correct_answer": "Mexico ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "USA",
      "Guatemala",
      "Costa Rica"
    ],
    "question": "From which country does Tabasco sauce originate?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502c3",
    "correct_answer": "Clove ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Husk",
      "Kernel",
      "Nibbet"
    ],
    "question": "What is a segment of garlic called?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502a0",
    "correct_answer": "Dr Pepper ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Lucozade",
      "Tango",
      "Sunny Delight"
    ],
    "question": "What soft drink is advertised with the slogan, \"What's the worst that could happen\"?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502f2",
    "correct_answer": "Deer ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Sheep",
      "Pig",
      "Goat"
    ],
    "question": "From what animal do we get venison?",
    "tags": [
      "animals",
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950248",
    "correct_answer": "Apple ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Blackberry",
      "Strawberry",
      "Banana"
    ],
    "question": "Which fruit is traditionally covered with toffee at a fairground?",
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95023f",
    "correct_answer": "Al dente ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tartilli",
      "Forte Benne",
      "Parpa Delle"
    ],
    "question": "Which Italian phrase is used to describe pasta cooked only until it offers a slight resistance when bitten?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c609c50d1a5e051325a67",
    "correct_answer": "India",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Scotland",
      "Cameroon",
      "Mauritius"
    ],
    "question": "Tandoori Chicken is a dish that is most associated with which part of the world?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502bc",
    "correct_answer": "Pasta ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Chicken",
      "Cheese",
      "Bread"
    ],
    "question": "What Is Ravioli? ",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "words",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950234",
    "correct_answer": "Ronald Mcdonald",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "The King",
      "Donald Burger",
      "Meato"
    ],
    "question": "Who is McDonald's mascot?",
    "tags": [
      "business",
      "advertising",
      "fictitious_characters",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c6148badf21197f98f771",
    "correct_answer": "United States",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Brunei",
      "Bahrain",
      "Vietnam"
    ],
    "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Mac 'N' Cheese?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60d550d1a5e051325a76",
    "correct_answer": "North Africa",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Ghana",
      "Belgium",
      "South America"
    ],
    "question": "Tagine is a dish that is most associated with which part of the world?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60bc50d1a5e051325a70",
    "correct_answer": "Japan",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Turkey",
      "Spain",
      "Estonia"
    ],
    "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Sushi?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60dc50d1a5e051325a78",
    "correct_answer": "Stamppot",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Ropa Vieja",
      "Meat Pie",
      "Ramen"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these dishes is most associated with Netherlands?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "the_netherlands",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9515cb",
    "correct_answer": "Mexico ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "China",
      "France",
      "Australia"
    ],
    "question": "From which country does the drink Tequila originate?",
    "tags": [
      "drink",
      "alcohol",
      "countries",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },{
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602cff4b176d54800e3c77",
    "correct_answer": "United Kingdom",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Australia",
      "Ireland",
      "Canada"
    ],
    "question": "In which country is the city of London?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602dd24b176d54800e3cad",
    "correct_answer": "Rio De Janeiro",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Caracas",
      "San Juan",
      "Montevideo"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Brazil?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d8c4b176d54800e3ca0",
    "correct_answer": "Buenos Aires",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Fortaleza",
      "Santiago",
      "Monterrey"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Argentina?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d924b176d54800e3ca2",
    "correct_answer": "United Arab Emirates",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Bahrain",
      "Egypt",
      "Jordan"
    ],
    "question": "In which country is the city of Abu Dhabi?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623742c0cb85f7ce9e949ded",
    "correct_answer": "Uganda",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Guinea",
      "Bangladesh",
      "Solomon Islands"
    ],
    "question": "Kampala is the capital city of which country?",
    "tags": [
      "capital_cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "625e9dff796f721e95543f38",
    "correct_answer": "Brazil",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Jamaica",
      "Faroe Islands",
      "Iran"
    ],
    "question": "Which country's flag can be described as 'Green with a yellow diamond in the center with a blue celestial globe.'?",
    "tags": [
      "flags",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602deb4b176d54800e3cb4",
    "correct_answer": "Marseille",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Düsseldorf",
      "Zürich",
      "Dublin"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in France?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "france",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d664b176d54800e3c95",
    "correct_answer": "Ireland",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "United Kingdom",
      "Australia",
      "United States"
    ],
    "question": "In which country is the city of Dublin?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623385150161109f922aabd7",
    "correct_answer": "Pacific Ocean",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Atlantic Ocean",
      "Arctic Ocean",
      "Indian Ocean"
    ],
    "question": "What ocean is found along the East Coast of Asia?",
    "tags": [
      "bodies_of_water",
      "oceans",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950aa4",
    "correct_answer": "United States of America",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "El Salvador",
      "Honduras",
      "Nicaragua"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Mexico?",
    "tags": [
      "central_america",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "625e9ee8796f721e95543f75",
    "correct_answer": "Three equal vertical bands of green white and red.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Three equal horizontal bands of red white and black.",
      "Red with a green five-pointed star in the center.",
      "Red field with a yellow sun in the center."
    ],
    "question": "What does the flag of Italy look like?",
    "tags": [
      "flags",
      "italy",
      "europe",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950aae",
    "correct_answer": "United States of America",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Mexico",
      "Belize",
      "Guatemala"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Canada?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d474b176d54800e3c8c",
    "correct_answer": "Moscow",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Zürich",
      "Barcelona",
      "Rotterdam"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Russia?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "russia",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950acf",
    "correct_answer": "Pakistan",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tajikistan",
      "Kyrgyzstan",
      "Thailand"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these countries borders India?",
    "tags": [
      "india",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d704b176d54800e3c98",
    "correct_answer": "China",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Sri Lanka",
      "Malaysia",
      "Taiwan"
    ],
    "question": "Hong Kong is a city in which country?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950af7",
    "correct_answer": "Canada",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Belize",
      "Guatemala",
      "Cuba"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these countries borders United States of America?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623740dbcb85f7ce9e949d29",
    "correct_answer": "Italy",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "France",
      "Greece",
      "Egypt"
    ],
    "question": "Rome is the capital city of which country?",
    "tags": [
      "capital_cities",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "625e9e03796f721e95543f39",
    "correct_answer": "Green",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Maroon",
      "Red",
      "Black"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these colors is included on the flag of Brazil?",
    "tags": [
      "flags",
      "south_america",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623b57e6fd6c701a92118386",
    "correct_answer": "USA",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Brazil",
      "Spain",
      "The UK"
    ],
    "question": "In which country would you find the Statue of Liberty?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623740bdcb85f7ce9e949d1d",
    "correct_answer": "India",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Thailand",
      "Solomon Islands",
      "Oman"
    ],
    "question": "New Delhi is the capital city of which country?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d0a4b176d54800e3c7a",
    "correct_answer": "Toronto",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "New York",
      "London",
      "Minneapolis-St Paul"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Canada?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "canada",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62374081cb85f7ce9e949d05",
    "correct_answer": "Germany",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Ukraine",
      "Poland",
      "Switzerland"
    ],
    "question": "Berlin is the capital city of which country?",
    "tags": [
      "capital_cities",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623b5794fd6c701a92118368",
    "correct_answer": "Athens",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Jerusalem",
      "Moscow",
      "Venice"
    ],
    "question": "In which city would you find the Acropolis?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623742cfcb85f7ce9e949df3",
    "correct_answer": "United Kingdom",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Russia",
      "Australia",
      "Belgium"
    ],
    "question": "London is the capital city of which country?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "625e9e30796f721e95543f45",
    "correct_answer": "Red with five yellow stars in the top left.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Blue with a yellow cross extending to the edges.",
      "Red with a black two headed eagle in the center.",
      "Green, with large white script and a sword."
    ],
    "question": "What does the flag of China look like?",
    "tags": [
      "flags",
      "china",
      "asia",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623385db62eaad73716a8c99",
    "correct_answer": "The Amazon ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "The Missouri",
      "The Mississippi",
      "The Rio Grande"
    ],
    "question": "What's the longest river in the Americas?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62373602cfe13103f55eb591",
    "correct_answer": "The United Kingdom",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Ukraine",
      "Uzbekistan",
      "Uganda"
    ],
    "question": "Which region of the world uses '.uk' at the end of its web addresses?",
    "tags": [
      "the_internet",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6237426acb85f7ce9e949dca",
    "correct_answer": "Madrid",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "San Marino",
      "Barcelona",
      "Seville"
    ],
    "question": "What is the capital city of Spain?",
    "tags": [
      "europe",
      "capital_cities",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6237408acb85f7ce9e949d09",
    "correct_answer": "Greece",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Luxembourg",
      "Georgia",
      "Serbia"
    ],
    "question": "Athens is the capital city of which country?",
    "tags": [
      "capital_cities",
      "cities",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6237353fcfe13103f55eb512",
    "correct_answer": "India",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "United Kingdom",
      "Indonesia",
      "Ireland"
    ],
    "question": "Which region of the world uses '.in' at the end of its web addresses?",
    "tags": [
      "the_internet",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62373ffacb85f7ce9e949ccf",
    "correct_answer": "China",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Japan",
      "North Korea",
      "Mongolia"
    ],
    "question": "Beijing is the capital city of which country?",
    "tags": [

    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623b57f0fd6c701a9211838a",
    "correct_answer": "Italy",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Russia",
      "New Zealand",
      "France"
    ],
    "question": "In which country would you find the city of Rome?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950a5c",
    "correct_answer": "Russia",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Bulgaria",
      "Lithuania",
      "Latvia"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Ukraine?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "625e9e33796f721e95543f46",
    "correct_answer": "Red",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Black",
      "Blue",
      "Green"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these colors is included on the flag of China?",
    "tags": [
      "flags",
      "china",
      "asia",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623742d6cb85f7ce9e949df6",
    "correct_answer": "Washington, D.C.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "New York",
      "Los Angeles",
      "Chicago"
    ],
    "question": "What is the capital city of The United States of America?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f950008",
    "correct_answer": "Rome",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Milan",
      "Naples",
      "Florence"
    ],
    "question": "In which city is the colosseum located?",
    "tags": [
      "tourist_attractions",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602cfc4b176d54800e3c76",
    "correct_answer": "Japan",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Philippines",
      "India",
      "China"
    ],
    "question": "Tokyo is a city in which country?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d694b176d54800e3c96",
    "correct_answer": "China",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Philippines",
      "Malaysia",
      "Cambodia"
    ],
    "question": "In which country is the city of Shenzhen?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d284b176d54800e3c83",
    "correct_answer": "Munich",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Valencia",
      "Budapest",
      "Milan"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Germany?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "germany",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6233892c0161109f922aacd0",
    "correct_answer": "Plate Tectonics ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Landslide",
      "The Big Bang",
      "Kercher's Theory"
    ],
    "question": "Which Theory Is Used To Explain Continental Drift?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602dbd4b176d54800e3caa",
    "correct_answer": "Perth",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Auckland",
      "Christchurch",
      "Queenstown"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Australia?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "australia",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623388b60161109f922aaca4",
    "correct_answer": "Pisa ",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Florence",
      "Naples",
      "Turin"
    ],
    "question": "Which Italian City Is Famous For Its Leaning Tower",
    "tags": [
      "tourist_attractions",
      "italy",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe0d",
    "correct_answer": "Asia",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Europe",
      "Africa",
      "North America"
    ],
    "question": "Which is the Earth's largest continent?",
    "tags": [
      "records",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff91",
    "correct_answer": "Beijing",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Hong Kong",
      "Shanghai",
      "Chengdu"
    ],
    "question": "What is the capital of China?",
    "tags": [
      "china",
      "capital_cities",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d174b176d54800e3c7e",
    "correct_answer": "Australia",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Ireland",
      "New Zealand",
      "Canada"
    ],
    "question": "Sydney is a city in which country?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d2c4b176d54800e3c84",
    "correct_answer": "Madrid",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Berlin",
      "Cologne",
      "Dublin"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Spain?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "spain",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602db94b176d54800e3ca9",
    "correct_answer": "United Kingdom",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "United States",
      "New Zealand",
      "Ireland"
    ],
    "question": "In which country is the city of Edinburgh?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "625e9fcd796f721e95543fb8",
    "correct_answer": "Blue with a yellow cross extending to the edges.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Red with a white crescent moon and star.",
      "Three equal horizontal bands of red blue and orange.",
      "Red with a black two headed eagle in the center."
    ],
    "question": "What does the flag of Sweden look like?",
    "tags": [
      "flags",
      "europe",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d5f4b176d54800e3c93",
    "correct_answer": "Copenhagen",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Milan",
      "Athens",
      "Munich"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Denmark?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602de44b176d54800e3cb2",
    "correct_answer": "India",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Mongolia",
      "Malaysia",
      "Japan"
    ],
    "question": "Where would you find the city of Delhi?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  }
  ]}
